Inventory of the Center for Civil Society International records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1948-2008. (Box 11-117)
  - Russia. Material relating primarily to the post-Soviet Russian federation
    - Localities
      - Ekaterinburg, 1995-1997 (Folder 81: 3)
      - Irkutsk, 1994-1997 (Folder 81: 4)
      - Khabarovsk, 1998 (Folder 81: 5)
      - Krasnodar, General, 1992-1998 (Folder 81: 6)
      - Krasnodar, Tallahassee-Krasnodar Sister City Program, 1985-1992 (Folder 81: 7)
      - Magadan area, undated (Folder 81: 8)
      - Moscow, 1992-1997 (Folder 81: 9)
      - Novosibirsk, 1997-1998 (Folder 81: 10)
      - Petrozavodsk, 1990 (Folder 81: 11)
      - Pskov, 1996-1997 (Folder 81: 12)
      - St. Petersburg, 1991-1997 (Folder 82: 1)
      - Samara, 1996-1997 (Folder 82: 2)
      - Siberia (Far East), 1990-1998 (Folder 82: 3)
      - Tver, 1996-1997 (Folder 82: 4)
      - Vladivostok, 1994 (Folder 82: 5)
    - Non-governmental organizations and nonprofit sector (Folder 82)
      - General, 1993-2000 (Folder 82: 6)
      - Charities Aid Foundation, 1992-1997 (Folder 82: 7)
      - Charities Aid Foundation, 1992-1997 (Folder 83: 1)
      - Contacts database, undated (Folder 83: 2)
      - Directories, 1995-1997 (Folder 83: 3)
      - Foundation for Social Innovations, 1989-1993 (Folder 83: 4)
      - Raduga Education and Information Center, 1994-1995 (Folder 83: 5)
      - Recognizing the Third Sector Conference, Moscow, Russia, 1993 (Folder 83: 6)
      - The Russian Non-Profit Sector, Center for Civil Society International publication, 1997 (Folder 83: 7)
      - Russian Peace Foundation, 1992 (Folder 83: 8)
      - United Way Moscow, 1992-1995 (Folder 84: 1)
      - World Learning, Inc., 1994 (Folder 84: 2)
      - Printed matter, 1995-1999 (Folder 84: 3)
    - Politics and government
      - General, 1992-1995 (Folder 84: 4)
      - Christian Democratic Party, 1991-1992 (Folder 84: 5)
      - Christian Democratic Union, 1990-1991 (Folder 84: 6)
      - Directories, 1991-1996 (Folder 84: 7-8)
      - Kazan Youth Political Club, 1994 (Folder 85: 1)
      - Rossiiskii Nauchnyi Fond, 1992-1993 (Folder 85: 2)
      - Tracy, Elizabeth Allen, "The Politicization of Russian Youth, 1985-1990," 1990 (Folder 85: 3)
      - Printed matter, 1988-1999 (Folder 85: 4)
    - Religion
      - General, 1996 (Folder 85: 5)
      - Aid to Russian Christians, 1996-1997 (Folder 85: 6)
      - Friends House Moscow, 1995-1997 (Folder 85: 7)
      - Peter Deyneka Russian Ministries, 1992-1998 (Folder 85: 8)
      - Russian-American Christian University, Moscow, 1994 (Folder 85: 9)
    - Telecommunications
      - General, 1994-1996 (Folder 86: 1)
      - Center for International Networking Initiatives, 1997 (Folder 86: 2)
      - English-Russian electronic dictionary, 1993 (Folder 86: 3)
      - International Bank of Ideas, undated (Folder 86: 4)
      - Internet dlia zhurnalistov, Publication written by Richard Upjohn and M. Holt Ruffin, 1997 (Folder 86: 5)
      - Levchik, Vasilii, 1994-1995 (Folder 86: 6)
      - Relkom, undated (Folder 86: 7)
      - Printed matter, 1994-2000 (Folder 86: 8-9)
    - United States contacts (general)
      - General, 1995-2004 (Folder 86: 10)
      - American Council of Teachers of Russian, 1991-1999 (Folder 86: 11)
      - Congress of Russian Americans, 1982-1993 (Folder 86: 12)
      - Connections/Sviazi (publication of United States Embassy, Moscow), 1994-1995 (Folder 87: 1)
      - Connections/Sviazi (publication of United States Embassy, Moscow), 1996-1997 (Folder 87: 2)
      - To Russia with Love, 1993 (Folder 87: 3)
      - Tolstoy Foundation, 1994 (Folder 87: 4)
      - University of Alaska. American Russian Center, 1995 (Folder 87: 5)
      - University of Arizona. Russian Abroad Program, 1994 (Folder 87: 6)
      - University of California. Berkeley-St. Petersburg Program, 1997 (Folder 87: 7)
    - Women and children
      - General, 1992-1996 (Folder 87: 8-9)
      - Alliance of American and Russian Women, 1993-1995 (Folder 87: 10)
      - Big Brothers/Big Sisters Moscow, 1992 (Folder 87: 11)
      - Information Center of the Independent Women's Forum, 1997 (Folder 87: 12)
      - International Committee for the Children of Chechnya, 1996-1997 (Folder 87: 13)
      - McCarter, Joan, "Women's Health in Crisis: Doctor, Patient and State and the Culture of Abortion in Post-Soviet Russia," 1997 (Folder 87: 14)
      - MiraMed Institute, 1992 (Folder 87: 15)
      - Ozon Centre, Moscow, undated (Folder 87: 16)
      - Russian Children's Welfare Society, 1991 (Folder 87: 17)
      - Save the Children, undated (Folder 87: 18)
  - Slovakia, 1998 (Folder 88: 1)
  - South Africa (Folder 88)
    - After Apartheid luncheon, Seattle, Washington, 1987 (Folder 88: 2)
    - Report from South Africa meeting, Seattle, Washington, 1987 (Folder 88: 3)
    - South Africa colloquium, Seattle, Washington, 1985 (Folder 88: 4)
    - South Africa Day, Skagit Valley College, Mount Vernon, Washington, 1985 (Folder 88: 5)
    - Tembaletu Transformation Project, 1988 (Folder 88: 6)
    - Triple Trust Organization, 1994-1997 (Folder 88: 7)
    - Printed matter, 1984 (Folder 88: 8)
  - Soviet Union
    - General, 1982-1991 (Folder 88: 9)
    - Communications
      - General, 1987-1989 (Folder 88: 10)
      - Freedom of Communications Committee, 1986-1990 (Folder 88: 11-12)
    - Culture
      - Art, 1988 (Folder 88: 13)
      - Book fairs, 1985-1988 (Folder 88: 14)
      - Olympic games, 1985 (Folder 88: 15)
      - PEN, 1988-1989 (Folder 88: 16)
      - Science, 1985-1988 (Folder 88: 17)
    - Disinformation, 1983-1989 (Folder 89: 1)
    - Dissidents
      - General, 1977-1986 (Folder 89: 2)
      - Demonstrations, 1987-1988 (Folder 89: 3)
      - National Endowment for Democracy/The Nation controversy, 1988 (Folder 89: 4)
    - Ecology, 1991-1992 (Folder 89: 5)
    - Education
      - General, 1970-1987 (Folder 89: 6-7)
      - World University Service, Moscow, undated (Folder 89: 8)
      - Youth in the USSR meeting, Seattle, Washington, 1987 (Folder 89: 9)
    - Emigrés, 1984-1991 (Folder 89: 10)
    - Exchanges
      - General, 1983-1989 (Folder 89: 11)
      - Ark Communications Institute, 1987 (Folder 90: 1)
      - Citizen Diplomacy, Inc., 1986-1987 (Folder 90: 2)
      - Citizens' Summit television dialogue, Leningrad, Russia, and Seattle, Washington, Publicity, 1985-1986 (Folder 90: 3)
      - Citizens' Summit television dialogue, Leningrad, Russia, and Seattle, Washington, Transcripts, 1985-1986 (Folder 90: 4)
      - Conference on Scholarly Exchanges with the USSR and Eastern Europe, Washington, D.C., 1979 (Folder 90: 5)
      - Conference on U.S.-Soviet Exchanges, Kennan Institute for Advanced Russian Studies, Washington, D.C., 1984 (Folder 90: 6)
      - Connect/US-USSR, 1991 (Folder 90: 7)
      - Divided Spouses Coalition, 1986-1987 (Folder 90: 8)
      - Exchange: US/USSR Conference, Seattle, Washington, 1986 (Folder 90: 9)
      - Letters from Soviet citizens, 1990-1991 (Folder 90: 10)
      - Organization for American-Soviet Exchanges, 1987 (Folder 91: 1)
      - President's U.S.-Soviet Exchange Initiative, 1985 (Folder 91: 2)
      - Rotary Goodwill Exchange, 1990 (Folder 91: 3)
      - Seattle, Washington, exchanges, 1985-1989 (Folder 91: 4)
      - Second Helping American-Soviet Citizen-to-Citizen Relief Program, 1990 (Folder 91: 5)
      - Skvortsov, Sergei. Gosteleradio interview with M. Holt Ruffin, 1987 (Folder 91: 6)
      - Soviet-American Exchange Center, 1984-1991 (Folder 91: 7)
      - Soviet-American Penfriend Exchange, 1990-1991 (Folder 91: 8)
      - Timofeev, Lev. Invitation to visit Seattle, Washington, 1988 (Folder 91: 9)
      - U.S. Embassy, Moscow, guidelines, undated (Folder 91: 10)
      - U.S.-Soviet Citizen Exchange symposia, 1990 (Folder 91)
        - Background material (Folder 91: 11)
        - Correspondence (Folder 91: 12)
        - Seattle, Washington, symposium (Folder 91: 13)
        - Questionnaire results (Folder 91: 14)
        - Report, Volume I (Folder 91)
          - Draft introduction (Folder 91: 15)
          - Master (Folder 91: 16)
          - Master appendices (Folder 91: 17)
          - Copies (Folder 91: 18)
        - Report, Volume II-Master (Folder 92: 1)
      - U.S.-Soviet Exchange Conference, Eisenhower World Affairs Institute, Gettysburg, Pennsylvania, 1988 (Folder 92: 2)
      - Visits International for Soviets and Americans (Folder 92)
        - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Folder 92: 3)
        - Issuances, 1986-1988 (Folder 92: 4)
        - Appeal for freedom of travel, 1989 (Folder 92: 5)
        - Congressional resolution, 1987 (Folder 92: 6)
        - Procedure chart for inviting a Soviet visitor to the United States, 1989 (Folder 92: 7)
        - Publicity, 1985-1990 (Folder 92: 8)
      - Washington, D.C.-Moscow Capitals Citizens' Exchange, 1986 (Folder 92: 9)
      - Wingspread Conference on Effective Citizen Education about the Soviet Union, Racine, Wisconsin, 1986 (Folder 92: 10)
      - Printed matter, 1984-1991 (Folder 93: 1-3)
    - Foreign relations (Folder 93)
      - American Committee on East-West Accord, 1978-1989 (Folder 93: 4-5)
      - American Committee on U.S.-Soviet Relations, 1986-1991 (Folder 93: 6)
      - Basic Principles of Relations between the United States and the USSR, 1972 (Folder 94: 1)
      - Center for Soviet-American Dialogue, 1985-1991 (Folder 94: 2)
      - Detente, 1985-1989 (Folder 94: 3)
      - Focus U.S./U.S.S.R. Conference, Seattle, Washington, 1987 (Folder 94: 4)
      - Leonhard, Wolfgang, The Kremlin and the West. Book orders, 1987-1988 (Folder 94: 5)
      - Public Summit '88, Seattle, Washington, 1988 (Folder 94: 6)
      - Stanford Program on International and Cross-Cultural Education, 1990 (Folder 94: 7)
      - United States. Central Intelligence Agency, 1976-1977 (Folder 94: 8)
      - Printed matter, 1963-1999 (Folder 94: 9-10)
    - Human rights
      - General, 1988-1990 (Folder 95: 1)
      - Andrei Sakharov Institute, 1985-1991 (Folder 95: 2)
      - Andrei Sakharov Memorial Congress, Moscow, Russia, 1991 (Folder 95: 3)
      - Bukovsky Foundation, 1986 (Folder 95: 4)
      - Comite Dr. A. Koryagin, 1989 (Folder 95: 5)
      - Human Rights and Nuclear War dinner, Seattle, Washington, 1986 (Folder 95: 6)
      - International Human Rights Conference, Vilnius, Lithuania, and Leningrad, Russia, General, 1990 (Folder 95: 7)
      - International Human Rights Conference, Vilnius, Lithuania, and Leningrad, Russia, Ruffin, M. Holt. Report, 1990 (Folder 95: 8)
      - International Parliamentary Group for Human Rights in the Soviet Union, 1986-1988 (Folder 95: 9)
      - International Symposium on Freedom of Movement for All, Moscow, Russia, 1989 (Folder 95: 10)
      - Press Club Glasnost, 1987-1988 (Folder 95: 11)
      - Samizdat Bulletin, 1983-1984 (Folder 96: 1)
      - Samizdat Bulletin, 1985 (Folder 96: 2)
      - Samizdat Bulletin, 1986 (Folder 96: 3)
      - Samizdat Bulletin, 1987 (Folder 96: 4)
      - Samizdat Bulletin, 1988-1990 (Folder 96: 5)
      - Seattle Peace and Freedom Coalition, 1984-1988 (Folder 96: 6)
      - Soviet view of human rights, 1978-1988 (Folder 96: 7)
      - Stolen Years (documentary film), 1998-2000 (Folder 97: 1)
      - USSR News Brief: Human Rights, 1988-1989 (Folder 97: 2)
      - Printed matter, 1984-1992 (Folder 97: 3-4)
    - Jews
      - General, 1982-1989 (Folder 97: 5)
      - Boulder Action for Soviet Jewry, 1987-1989 (Folder 97: 6)
      - Emigration, 1986-1989 (Folder 97: 7)
      - Jackson-Vanik amendment, 1989-1991 (Folder 97: 8)
      - National Interreligious Task Force on Soviet Jewry, 1974-1986 (Folder 97: 9)
      - Solomon Michoels Jewish Cultural Center, undated (Folder 97: 10)
    - Journalism
      - General (Russian-language newspapers), 1990 (Folder 98: 1-2)
      - Express-Chronicle, 1987-1989 (Folder 98: 3)
      - Moscow News, 1991-1992 (Folder 98: 4)
    - Law
      - General, 1986 (Folder 98: 5)
      - American Bar Association/Association of Soviet Lawyers exchanges, 1986-1987 (Folder 98: 6)
      - American Bar Association/Association of Soviet Lawyers exchanges, 1988 (Folder 98: 7)
      - American Bar Association/Association of Soviet Lawyers exchanges, 1989 (Folder 98: 8)
    - Nationalities
      - General, 1991 (Folder 99: 1)
      - Blacks, 1986-1989 (Folder 99: 2)
      - Crimean Tatars, 1984-1988 (Folder 99: 3)
    - Non-governmental organizations
      - General, 1988 (Folder 99: 4)
      - Avers, undated (Folder 99: 5)
      - Center for Democracy in the USSR, 1984-1990 (Folder 99: 6)
      - Civil Society: USA. Russian translation of World Without War Council publication, 1990 (Folder 99: 7)
      - Foundation for Social Innovations, 1989 (Folder 99: 8)
      - Golubka, 1989-1991 (Folder 99: 9)
      - Guide to U.S. Organizations Which Can Facilitate Independent Contacts in the Soviet Union. World Without War Council publication, 1989 (Folder 99: 10)
      - Information and Consultation Center on Working Movements, 1990 (Folder 99: 11)
      - Institute for Soviet-American Relations handbook of organizations, edition, 1983 (Folder 100: 1)
      - Institute for Soviet-American Relations handbook of organizations, edition, 1986 (Folder 100: 2)
      - Institute for Soviet-American Relations handbook of organizations, edition, 1990 (Folder 100: 3)
      - Neformalniye: A Guide to Independent Organizations and Contacts in the Soviet Union. World Without War Council publication, 1990 (Folder 100)
        - Working materials (Folder 100: 4)
        - Drafts (Folder 100: 5)
        - Master (Folder 100: 6)
        - Copies (Folder 100: 7)
        - Russian translation (Folder 101: 1)
      - Samantha Smith Center, 1990-1992 (Folder 101: 2)
      - Shield, 1991 (Folder 101: 3)
      - Soviet Fund for Charity and Health, 1990 (Folder 101: 4)
    - Peace movement
      - Moscow Trust Group
        - Declaration of principles, 1987 (Folder 101: 5)
        - Batovrin, Sergei. Writings, 1983 (Folder 101: 6)
        - Reitman, Mark. Writings, 1985-1986 (Folder 101: 7)
        - Return Address: Moscow (bulletin), 1984-1985 (Folder 101: 8)
        - General. Memoranda, correspondence, circulated material, printed matter, 1982-1985 (Folder 101: 9-12)
        - General. Memoranda, correspondence, circulated material, printed matter, 1986-1988 (Folder 102: 1-3)
      - Printed matter, 1981-1983 (Folder 102: 4)
    - Politics and government
      - Communist Party, 1970-1986 (Folder 102: 5)
      - Democratic Labor Movement, undated (Folder 102: 6)
      - Democratic Union, 1988-1989 (Folder 102: 7)
      - Elections, 1986-1989 (Folder 102: 8)
      - Free Labor Party, 1990 (Folder 102: 9)
      - Glasnost', 1986-1990 (Folder 102: 10)
      - Moscow Popular Front, 1989 (Folder 102: 11)
      - Pamiat', 1987-1989 (Folder 103: 1)
      - Political parties and contacts, 1990 (Folder 103: 2)
      - Political structure, 1973-1989 (Folder 103: 3)
      - Transnational Radical Party, 1990 (Folder 103: 4)
      - Printed matter, 1981-1992 (Folder 103: 5-7)
    - Religion
      - General, 1983-2000 (Folder 103: 8)
      - Association of Christians in Business, Moscow, 1991-1992 (Folder 104: 1)
      - Episcopal Church Soviet Studies Program, 1986 (Folder 104: 2)
      - Friendship Press, 1987 (Folder 104: 3)
      - Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1989 (Folder 104: 4)
      - Issachar Frontier Missions Research, 1984 (Folder 104: 5)
      - Krishna movement, 1987 (Folder 104: 6)
      - National Council of Churches, 1984-1988 (Folder 104: 7)
      - Religious prisoners of conscience, 1984-1988 (Folder 104: 8)
    - Sister city programs
      - General, 1986-1989 (Folder 104: 9)
      - Lists of sister cities, 1986-1987 (Folder 104: 10)
      - Salem (Oregon)-Simferopol program, 1986-1989 (Folder 104: 11)
      - U.S.-Soviet Sister Cities Conference, Seattle, Washington, 1987 (Folder 105)
        - General (Folder 105: 1)
        - Jewish Federation of Greater Seattle report (Folder 105: 2)
        - Seattle Peace and Freedom Coalition statements (Folder 105: 3)
        - Press coverage (Folder 105: 4)
    - Travel
      - General, 1984-1989 (Folder 105: 5)
      - Manuals, 1986-1990 (Folder 105: 6)
      - Ruffin, M. Holt, and Marvin and Michele Stern. Reports on trips, 1986 (Folder 105: 7)
      - Soviet regulations, 1984 (Folder 105: 8)
    - Official Soviet publications, mainly English-language pamphlets, arranged by subject (Folder 106)
      - Children and youth, 1985-1989 (Folder 106: 1)
      - Constitution and laws, 1981-1990 (Folder 106: 2)
      - Culture, 1985-1990 (Folder 106: 3-4)
      - Economy, 1985-1990 (Folder 107: 1)
      - Environment, 1987-1989 (Folder 107: 2)
      - Foreign relations, 1981-1990 (Folder 107: 3-4)
      - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 1985-1990 (Folder 107: 5)
      - History, 1981-1990 (Folder 108: 1-2)
      - Human rights, 1981-1989 (Folder 108: 3)
      - Journalism, 1988-1991 (Folder 108: 4)
      - Marxism-Leninism, 1963-1989 (Folder 108: 5)
      - Marxism-Leninism, 1963-1989 (Folder 109: 1)
      - Peace and disarmament, 1982-1989 (Folder 109: 2-4)
      - Perestroika, 1988-1989 (Folder 110: 1-2)
      - Politics and government, 1985-1990 (Folder 110: 3)
      - Religion, 1980-1989 (Folder 110: 4)
      - Republics and regions, 1982-1989 (Folder 111: 1-2)
      - Science and technology, 1988 (Folder 111: 3)
      - Society and social policy, 1987-1989 (Folder 111: 4)
      - Sports, 1988 (Folder 111: 5)
      - Women, 1985-1990 (Folder 111: 6)
      - Yearbooks and statistics, 1982-1989 (Folder 112: 1-2)
  - Tajikistan
    - General, 1995-1999 (Folder 112: 3)
    - Human rights, 1991 (Folder 112: 4)
  - Transcaucasia. Material not limited to a single country in the region
    - General, 1997 (Folder 112: 5)
    - Caucasian Institute for Peace, Democracy and Development, 1994 (Folder 112: 6)
    - Issachar Frontier Missions Research, 1984 (Folder 112: 7)
  - Turkey, 2007 (Folder 112: 8)
  - Turkmenistan
    - General, 1990-1997 (Folder 113: 1)
    - Human rights, 1993 (Folder 113: 2)
  - Ukraine
    - General, 1988-2001 (Folder 113: 3)
    - Americans for Human Rights in Ukraine, 1990-1991 (Folder 113: 4)
    - Boston Kiev Sister City Association, 1996 (Folder 113: 5)
    - Children of Chornobyl Relief Fund, 1990-1993 (Folder 113: 6)
    - Cincinnati-Kharkhiv Sister City Project, 1996 (Folder 113: 7)
    - Dr. F. P. Haaz Social Assistance Fund, 1990 (Folder 113: 8)
    - Ecoforum Kiev 95, 1995 (Folder 113: 9)
    - Economics Education and Research Consortium Ukraine Economics M.A. Program, University of Kiev-Mohyla Academy, 1997-1998 (Folder 113: 10-11)
    - Education reform, 1996 (Folder 113: 12)
    - Eurasia Foundation Kiev Regional Office, 1994 (Folder 113: 13)
    - Foundation for International Professional Exchange, 2000 (Folder 113: 14)
    - Green Party, 1990 (Folder 113: 15)
    - Green World/Zeleny Svit, 1990 (Folder 113: 16)
    - International Society for Human Rights-Odessa, 1995-1996 (Folder 113: 17)
    - Journalism and broadcasting, 1996 (Folder 113: 18)
    - Kiev contacts, 1992-1998 (Folder 114: 1)
    - Kyiv FreeNet, 1995 (Folder 114: 2)
    - Kyiv Post, 1998 (Folder 114: 3)
    - Non-governmental organizations, 1989-1997 (Folder 114: 4-6)
    - Petro Jacyk Educational Foundation, 1993-1994 (Folder 114: 7)
    - Project on Economic Reform in Ukraine, 1992 (Folder 114: 8)
    - Smoloskyp, 1986-1988 (Folder 114: 9)
    - Telecommunications, 1994 (Folder 114: 10)
    - U.S.-Ukraine Foundation, 1992-2000 (Folder 115: 1)
    - Ukrainian American Bar Association, 1993-1995 (Folder 115: 2)
    - Ukrainian-American Educational Exchange Association, undated (Folder 115: 3)
    - Ukrainian American Police Association, 1993-1994 (Folder 115: 4)
    - Ukrainian Center for Human Rights, 1995-1996 (Folder 115: 5)
    - Ukrainian Center for Independent Political Research, 1997 (Folder 115: 6)
    - Ukrainian Congress Committee of America, 1991-2000 (Folder 115: 7)
    - Ukrainian Information Center, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1994-1996 (Folder 115: 8)
    - Ukrainian Institute of Modern Art, undated (Folder 115: 9)
    - Ukrainian National Association, 1996-1998 (Folder 115: 10)
    - Ukrainian Peace Committee, 1986-1988 (Folder 115: 11)
    - Ukrainian Society Chernobyl Children, 1993 (Folder 115: 12)
    - Ukrainian Student Association of the U.S.A., 1997 (Folder 115: 13)
    - Vozmozhnosti Interneta dlia prepodavatelei ekonomicheskikh distsiplii. Center for Civil Society International publication by Richard Upjohn and M. Holt Ruffin, undated (Folder 115: 14)
    - World Congress of Free Ukrainians, 1987-1988 (Folder 115: 15)
    - Printed matter, 1984-1998 (Folder 116: 1-2)
  - Uzbekistan
    - General, 1997-1998 (Folder 116: 3)
    - Birlik (Uzbek Popular Front), 1989-1990 (Folder 116: 4)
    - Economic reform, 1998 (Folder 116: 5)
    - Friends of Uzbekistan, 1994 (Folder 116: 6)
    - Human rights, 1994 (Folder 116: 7)
    - Information Consulting Center, Samarkand, 1995 (Folder 116: 8)
    - International Museum of Peace and Solidarity, Samarkand, 1996-2000 (Folder 116: 9)
    - Non-governmental organizations, 1996-1998 (Folder 116: 10)
    - Obshchestvo prav cheloveka Uzbekistana, 1995 (Folder 116: 11)
    - Seattle-Tashkent Sister City Association, 1972-1998 (Folder 117: 1-2)
    - United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees Regional Conference, Tashkent, Uzbekistan, 1997 (Folder 117: 3)
  - Vietnam (Folder 117)
    - Vietnam Committee on Human Rights, 1987 (Folder 117: 4)
    - Printed matter, 1965-1982 (Folder 117: 5)
  - Yugoslavia, 1986-1999 (Folder 117: 6)